followup.cc 2016-04-09

# FollowUp.cc | Privacy Policy

#### FollowUp is a lightweight email reminder service. This policy describes the types of personal information we may collect and how we use it to provide the FollowUp service.

By using FollowUp, you agree to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this policy. You should know:

* We collect limited account information to maintain your account and reminders on our servers.  
* We will never rent, sell or share information that personally identifies you for marketing purposes without your express permission.  
* You can update your account information and preferences at any time.

To comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, at this time FollowUp is only available to users who are at least 13 years old. If you are under 13, please do not use the FollowUp service.

### What types of personal information do we collect and how do we use it?

Account information. When you register with FollowUp, we will request some personal information, including your email address and password to create your account. Your password will be maintained on our system in an encrypted form.

Reminder contents and usage. The contents of your FollowUp account are stored and maintained on FollowUp servers in order to provide the service. Because we keep back-up copies of data for the purposes of recovery from errors or system failure, residual copies of reminders may remain on our systems for some time, even after you have deleted information or after the termination of your account. FollowUp employees do not access the content of any reminders unless you specifically request them to do so (for example, if you are having technical difficulties accessing your account) or if required by law, to maintain our system, or to protect FollowUp or the public.

We also may collect information about the use of your account, such as how much storage you are using, how often you log in and other information related to your registration and use of FollowUp. Information displayed or clicked on in your FollowUp account (including UI elements, links, and other information) is also recorded. We use this information internally to deliver the best possible service to you, such as improving the FollowUp user interface.

FollowUp will never sell, rent or share your personal information with any third parties for marketing purposes without your express permission.

### Cookies & log information

Cookies. A cookie is a small data file that is sent to your computer when you first visit a website. As with most website cookies, our cookies include an identification number that is unique to the computer you are using. This identifier helps us better understand our user base and how they are using our site and services.

When you visit FollowUp and create a FollowUp account, we set and access cookies on your computer. We use cookies for a number of reasons, such as recognizing you when you visit the site, displaying the site according to your chosen user settings for language, and maintaining the security of your account. We may also use the cookies to collect aggregated information about the use of FollowUp to maintain, analyze and improve the service. If you set your browser so that it refuses cookies, you will not be able to use the FollowUp service.

Log information. When you use your FollowUp account, we collect certain information (the same information that most web sites log when they are accessed). This information, contained in the "header" of your request to access the FollowUp page, usually includes the browser type you used, your Internet Protocol address, and the date and time of day. In addition, we log the unique ID provided by our cookie and the URL of the last site you visited.

As a basic matter, we need this information to help us provide our services to you. For example, we need to validate your identity in order to maintain the security of your reminders. We also need to know what Internet Protocol address your query came from so we can send the appropriate pages back to you.

In addition, we log this information for internal business purposes. For example, this log information helps us determine how well our services are working so we can continually improve the quality of FollowUp. The log information is also important for security, audit, quality improvement, and other internal business purposes.

### How we may contact you

FollowUp may send you information related to your FollowUp account or FollowUp services. Because we believe such information is important, you will not be given the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

### Transfer of information

Personal information collected by FollowUp may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which FollowUp maintains facilities. By using FollowUp, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of FollowUp, such as acquisition by or merger with another company. In such an event, FollowUp will notify you with an opt-out option before information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Updating your information

You can change your FollowUp account settings at any time in the "Settings" section of your account.

You can terminate your account at any time, by going to the Billing page. We typically deactivate accounts within two business days of such requests. You should be aware, however, that residual copies of information may remain stored on our systems even after the deletion of information or the termination of your account.

We hope you will enjoy using FollowUp. 

### Program Policies

To uphold the quality and reputation of FollowUp, your use of FollowUp is subject to these program policies. If you are found to be in violation of our policies at any time, as determined by FollowUp in its sole discretion, we may warn you or suspend or terminate your account. 

Please note that we may change our policies at any time, and pursuant to our Terms of Use, it is your responsibility to keep up-to-date with and adhere to the policies posted here. 

### Prohibited Actions

In addition to (and/or as some examples of) the violations described in the Terms of Use, users may not: 

  * Send, upload, distribute or disseminate or offer to do the same with respect to any unlawful, defamatory, harassing, abusive, fraudulent, infringing, obscene, or otherwise objectionable content 
  * Intentionally distribute viruses, worms, defects, Trojan horses, corrupted files, hoaxes, or any other items of a destructive or deceptive nature 
  * Transmit content that may be harmful to minors 
  * Illegally transmit another's intellectual property or other proprietary information without such owner's or licensor's permission 
  * Use FollowUp to violate the legal rights (such as rights of privacy and publicity) of others 
  * Promote or encourage illegal activity 
  * Interfere with other FollowUp users' enjoyment of the Service 
  * Create multiple user accounts in connection with any violation of the Agreement or create user accounts by automated means or under false or fraudulent pretenses 
  * Sell, trade, resell or otherwise exploit for any unauthorized commercial purpose or transfer any FollowUp account 
  * Modify, adapt, translate, or reverse engineer any portion of the FollowUp Service 
  * Remove any copyright, trademark or other proprietary rights notices contained in or on the FollowUp Service 
  * Reformat or frame any portion of the web pages that are part of the FollowUp Service 

### Security

You must promptly notify FollowUp of any breach of security related to the Services, including but not limited to unauthorized use of your password or account. 

### Safe Harbor

FollowUp.cc complies with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. FollowUp.cc has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles, the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles shall govern, except in the case of data transfers from the EEA and Switzerland, which are covered under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view our certification page, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

### Transfer of information

Personal information collected by FollowUp may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which FollowUp maintains facilities. By using FollowUp, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country, except in the case of transfers from the EEA and Switzerland, which are covered under the Safe Harbor Frameworks. 

In compliance with the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, we endeavor to resolve all complaints about privacy and the collection or use of customer information. If you have questions about our participation in the Safe Harbor program or have a complaint, please send an e-mail to: [support@followup.cc](mailto:support@followup.cc)

Under the Safe Harbor program, any unresolved privacy complaints can be referred to an independent dispute resolution mechanism. We use the BBB EU Safe Harbor Program, which is operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you feel that we have not satisfactorily addressed your complaint, you can visit the BBB EU Safe Harbor Program web site at <http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints> for more information on how to file a complaint.
